我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来  我只是个普通的鉴证专员
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
but secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
我让杀害母亲的凶手自食其果
I hunted down the man who killed my mother,
但我们的世界也因此出现了新的威胁
but in doing so, I opened up our world to new threats,
我是唯一来得及阻止他们的人
and I am the only one fast enough to stop them.
我叫闪电侠
I am The Flash!
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
我看见已发生的情景
I get a vision of something that's already happened,
然后就消失了
and then it's gone.
我不想让任何人知道
I don't want anyone to know about this.
当你在中城制造了奇点
When you created the Singularity
你也在我们两个世界之间
above Central City, you also created a breach
制造了一个缺口
between my world and yours, connecting our two earths.
中城52个缺口  最大的
52 breaches in Central City and the biggest one
恰好就在我们的地下室
just happens to be in our basement.
昨晚闯进大楼的人
The person who broke into my facility last night
是哈里森·威尔斯
was Harrison Wells.
放下他
Hey, put him down!
你是什么人
Who the hell are you?
大家好
Hello.
地球二
对于不认识我的人来说
For those of you who don't know me,
我叫哈里森·威尔斯
my name is Harrison Wells.
八个月前
今天  我们进入了未来
Today, the future has arrived.
我们的城市见证了奇迹
Our city has seen incredible--
见证了不可能  即超能力者
impossible things: meta-humans--men and women--
身怀绝技的男人和女人
with extraordinary abilities:
他们有的可以直冲云霄
the ability to soar above buildings,
有人可以超光速奔跑
to run faster than the speed of light.
不幸的是  大多数的超能力人
Unfortunately, most of these meta-humans
选择了错误的道路  黑暗的道路
have chosen the wrong path with these powers, a dark path.
我的尖端科研实验室团队和我都致力于
My team and I at S.T.A.R. Labs are committed
紧跟时代  帮助大家度过危险时期
to keeping up with these perilous times,
请允许我向大家介绍全新系列的
and so may I present to you our new line
帮助大家发现超能力人的应用
of meta-human awareness apps?
这项科技能让大家
This technology will allow you
时刻监测超能力人的踪迹
to instantly detect the presence of a meta-human.
如果有极速者靠近  立刻会收到提醒
You'll be instantly alerted to an approaching speedster,
比如极速  或者...
like Zoom or like...
闪电侠
Flash.
欢迎你  闪电侠
Welcome, Flash.
告诉他们真相  威尔斯博士
Tell them the truth, Dr. Wells.
过去两年里这座城市发生的一切
Everything that has happened to this city the past two years
都是拜你所赐
is because of you.
是你创造了我们所有的超能力者
You created all of us metas.
你创造了极速
You created Zoom.
我创造了极速
I created Zoom?
第一个超能力人出现前十一小时
11 hours before the first meta sighting,
这所实验室下方无声无息的发生了
enormous blasts of dark matter radiation
巨大的暗物质辐射爆炸
were silently expelled beneath this lab.
抱歉  闪电侠  我想你跑得太快
I'm sorry, Flash, I believe all this fast running
导致你头脑也不太清晰了
may have scrambled your brain.
你没有为自己的错误造成的后果承担责任
You take no responsibility for the wreckage your mistakes have caused.
承认吧  威尔斯
Admit it, Wells,
或许你可以真正帮上我的忙
and then maybe you can truly help me do something about it.
我帮你  因为我是史上最伟大的科技企业家
Help you, because I'm the greatest tech entrepreneur of all time?
你才是超级英雄
You're the superhero,
如果你尽好本分  阻止极速
and we would all be safe
我们大家都能平平安安
if you would just do your job and stop Zoom.
我想可以说极速者感应器起作用了
Well, I guess it's safe to say the speedster sensors work.
-你还好吗  爸爸  -我没事  亲爱的
- You okay, Dad? - I'm fine, sweetie.
我刚才说到哪儿了
Now where was I?
哦对了  未来
Oh, that's right, the future.
威尔斯传
拿着自己传记的感觉真奇怪
Very strange to be holding your autobiography,
尤其还不是你写的
especially when you didn't write it
并且写的也不是你
and it's not about you.
凯特琳·斯诺博士  西斯科·拉蒙
Dr. Caitlin Snow, Cisco Ramon,
来见见哈里森·威尔斯博士
meet Dr. Harrison Wells
地球二来的
from Earth-2.
-你好  -你们好
- Hi. - Hi.
那我就直说了
So let me get this straight.
你是杀了他母亲  并且造成了
You're the doppelganger of the man who murdered his mom
罗尼和艾迪的死的那个人的分身
and is responsible for both Ronnie and Eddie's deaths?
对  但他不是我们认识的威尔斯博士的分身
Yeah, but he's not even the doppelganger of the Dr. Wells that we knew
因为那个威尔斯博士的身体
because that Dr. Wells' body had been taken over
被逆闪电夺取了  也就是艾尔伯德·斯旺
by the Reverse Flash, who was really Eobard Thawne
也就是艾迪未来的远亲
and Eddie's distant relative from the future.
我一点没听懂  我就是我
Yeah, I didn't follow any of that. I'm my own man.
我跟你母亲和你朋友瑞奇的死没有任何关系
I had nothing to do with the murder of your mother or your friend Ricky.
-他的名字叫罗尼  -他也一样
- His name was Ronnie. - Him either.
你说你能证明自己的身份
You told me you have proof of your identity?
我穿过传送门的时候这东西差点打到我
This almost hit me when I went through the portal.
你们楼下稳定的缺口和我的星球上的
Your stabilized breach downstairs connects directly
尖端科研实验室直接相连
to the S.T.A.R. Labs on my Earth.
技术上来说  这可能是我的
Technically, this could be mine,
但我想对你做些测试
but I want to run some tests on you.
我的基因和地球一上的一定是完全相同的
I'll be genetically indistinguishable from my Earth-1 counterpart.
你们的测试什么证明不了
Your tests will reveal nothing.
太好了  还是要测试
Great! Still gonna run 'em.
请便
Be my guest.
我们干嘛要听他讲话
Why are we even listening to him?
你怎么知道他不像之前那个一样邪恶
How do we know he's not evil like the other guy?
他昨晚救了我的命
He saved my life last night.
问题是为什么
The question is why.
我想你穿越不同次元
I'm guessing you didn't travel between dimensions
不只是想见闪电侠
just to meet The Flash.
这就是我的意图
That's exactly what I did.
我是来帮你的  巴里
I came here to help you, Barry,
帮你打败你的宿敌
to stop your greatest enemy.
他已经做到了
He already did that.
我说的不是逆闪电
I'm not talking about Reverse Flash.
我说的是极速
I'm talking about Zoom.
看来你已经听说过他了
I see you've already heard of him.
是的  极速一直在把超能力者
Yeah, Zoom has been sending meta-humans
从你的世界送到这边来与我战斗
from your world through the breaches to fight me.
他们只是病症
Well, they're the symptoms.
极速才是瘟疫
Zoom's the plague,
他感染了我的世界  现在又冲你的世界而来
one that's infected my world, and now he's coming for yours.
你对极速了解多少
What do you know about Zoom?
无所不知
Everything.
我创造了极速
I created Zoom.
地球二的所有超能力者都是因我才出现的
I'm responsible for all the Earth-2 meta-humans,
我无视这个事实很久了
a fact I've ignored for far too long,
但现在我要着手处理了
but now I'm doing something about it.
我们现在对抗裂口的成绩很不错
Yeah, well, we're batting a thousand against these breachers.
你们的成绩很不错吗  克里斯科
You're batting a thousand, Crisco?
你们遇到过几例
What's your sample size?
十
Ten?
还是更少
Less?
极速对速度非常痴迷
Zoom is obsessed with speed.
他绝不会允许多元宇宙中还有其他极速者
He will never allow there to be another speedster in the multiverse,
他会持续不断地送超能力者来这里
and he's gonna keep sending these metas here,
一个接一个的  全都只有一个目标
one after the next, all with the same goal:
杀死闪电侠
to kill The Flash
除非我们一起阻止了他
unless we stop him together.
上一次我们听从一个有你这张脸的人
Last time we listened to a guy with your face,
发生了很不好的事情
some bad things went down.
我们失去了我们所在乎的人
We lost people we cared about.
所有人都会失去一些在乎的人  斯诺
Everyone loses someone they care about, Snow.
真正磨练人格的是他们走了之后你怎么办
The real test of character is what you do once they're gone.
乔  把枪放下
Joe! Put the gun down!
他怎么还活着  你怎么还活着
How is he still alive? How are you still alive?
我不知道  因为你打偏了
I don't know, because you missed?
我在阻止他开枪打你
Hey, I'm trying to keep him from shooting you.
你这是帮倒忙呢  咱出去走走好吗
You're not helping. Let's take a walk, all right?
一切都好
It's all good.
我们认识一个能证实他言论的人
We know someone who can verify everything that this guy just said.
当心点
Be careful.
不知道你们这里有没有大贝利汉堡店
I don't suppose you have a Big Belly Burger in this universe, do you?
这太难以置信了
This isn't happening.
我知道这信息量很大
I know that this is a lot to take in,
但是刚才屋里那个人  不是威尔斯
but that guy back in that room, that's not Wells.
麦吉博士发誓说她看到了威尔斯
Dr. McGee swore she saw Wells.
他闯进了水星实验室
He broke into Mercury Labs.
什么  为什么你不告诉我
What? Why didn't you tell me this?
因为我不相信她
Because I didn't believe her.
我都不想有威尔斯还活着的想法
I didn't even want to consider Wells was alive.
艾迪将那个威尔斯的存在抹消了
Eddie erased that Wells from existence.
这男的他...他是别人
This guy is-he's someone else,
并且他说他是来帮我阻止极速的
and he says he's here to help us stop Zoom.
你怎么能直视得了他
How can you even look at him?
你觉得这对我来说很容易吗
You think this is easy for me?
这男人的长相  行为  声音都与那个
The guy in there looks, moves, sounds exactly like the guy
将一把刀捅入我母亲心脏的人一模一样
that drove a knife through my mother's heart.
我必须要克制自己不去杀了他
I have to resist the urge to kill him.
我在尽最大努力越过这障碍  好吗
I'm trying my best to get past that, okay?
你开枪打他  这没有帮助
You shooting him-that's not helping.
在失去这一切之后  我还以为最起码
After all our losses, I thought at least
我们能摆脱威尔斯
we were free of Wells.
我只想有那么一周
I just want one week
没有某个从过去来的人给我们个"惊喜"
where we're not surprised by somebody from our past.
我最好去和艾瑞丝说下
I better go fill in Iris.
祝你好运
Good luck.
中城新闻图报
幸灾乐祸吧  琳达
I hope you're happy, Linda.
坦纳的律师威胁要起诉我们
Tanner's lawyers are threatening to sue us.
抱歉  老大
I'm sorry, Chief.
我不管坦纳投了多少个好球
I don't care how many touchdowns Tanner throws.
我才不会采访一个打妻子的肌肉混蛋
I'm not interviewing some roided out jerk who hit his wife
除非他被指控家庭暴力了
unless it's to hold him accountable for domestic violence.
好吧  写你的报道吧  帕克
All right, run your story, Park.
体育版块以前可没这么多事
The sports page used to be a lot less complicated.
她投球了
She shoots.
她得分了
She scores.
拉尔金是我效力过的最好的编辑
Larkin is the best editor I have been worked for.
只不过  时不时的
It's just, every once in a while,
你要提醒下他  这已经是二十一世纪了
you have to remind him it's the 21st century.
但那不是真的他
But that's not really him,
不是艾迪牺牲性命阻止的那个威尔斯
the Wells who Eddie gave his life to stop?
显然不是
Apparently not.
这都成中城的日常了  对吧
That's life in Central City these days, right?
-你没事吧  -爸爸  我没事  真的
- You sure? - Dad, I'm fine, really.
那就好
Good.
我要你保持下去
I want to keep you that way.
-爸爸  -拿去
- Dad. - Take it.
我教你怎么用是有原因的
I taught you how to use it for a reason.
我也希望巴里是正确的
And I'm praying that Barry's right
这个威尔斯对我们无害
and this Wells means us no harm.
去年  你有艾迪照顾你
Last year, you had Eddie to look out for you,
但是现在...
but now...
你不可能谋杀一个
you can't murder somebody
所有人都认为死了的人  对吧
that everybody thinks is dead, right?
放起来吧
Put it away.
吉特咖啡店
你知道当我说我想喝一杯的时候
You do realize that when I said i wanted a drink,
我指的不是拿铁吧
I didn't mean a latte, right?
我说的是喝酒
I was talking about alcohol.
那种喝一杯就让你忘却烦恼的酒
Like, mind-numbing alcohol.
你得给他一次机会
All right, look, you got give him a chance, okay?
他不是极速者
He's not a speedster.
他只是从平行宇宙来的一个普通人
He's just a regular, normal guy from another universe.
我从没想过我会这么怀念时间旅行
I never thought I'd miss time travel.
时间旅行啊
Time travel, huh?
-真巧啊  -你好
- Hey! Are you kidding? - Hi!
现在还有能时间旅行的超能力者了吗
Is there a meta-human who can time travel?
不  没有  时间旅行不是真的
Time--no. Time travel's not real.
要是真的就太好了
Cause that would be pretty cool!
我可不觉得这有什么好的
Not so sure about that.
帕蒂  你认识西斯科·拉蒙吧
Patty, you know Cisco Ramon, right?
你是中城警局针对超能力者请来的科学顾问吧
Yeah, you're the scientific advisor on meta-humans to the CCPD, right?
-没错  就是我  -很高兴见到你
- Yeah, that's me. - Nice.
巴里  你知道吗  鲨鱼王那事我是对的
Hey, Barr, did you hear I was right about King Shark?
鲨鱼王  这名字不错  我喜欢她
King Shark? Nice name. I like her.
是啊  鲨鱼王差点吃了闪电侠
Yeah, yeah, King Shark almost ate The Flash.
闪电侠肯定不会这么弱的
Oh, nah, I'm sure The Flash had it handled.
我当时就在现场  我目睹了一切
Oh, no, I was there. I saw it all.
有个穿连帽衫的人救了他
Some hooded guy saved his life.
你目睹了一切  没受到什么刺激吗
Wait, and you're not, like, traumatized or anything?
我刚刚目睹了一个半人半鲨的生物
I just watched a half man-half shark
和史上速度最快的人来了一场恶战
take on the fastest man alive.
我爱死这座城市了
I love this city.
不好意思
See...sorry.
队长给我发短信了
Oh, uh, Captain just texted me.
他想让我把警方报告写了
He wants me to write my police report.
你想跟我一起写吗
Uh, you maybe want to write it with me?
今晚不行  我有别的事
Uh, I can't tonight. I'm busy. Um, yeah, sorry.
好吧
Oh, yeah, okay.
我要研究一些东西
I've just got science stuff.
我要研究一些很重要的东西
Stuff I gotta science the stuff out of.
也许下次可以
Maybe next time.
-好  那就下次  -好啊
- Yeah! Coolio. - Yeah.
我就不跟你们一起喝咖啡了
But I'm gonna actually skip the coffee
我先回去开始写报告了
and go get a head start, so...
很高兴见到你
Good to see you guys.
我也是
Yeah.
-你没搞错吧  -别挤兑我了
- For real? - Stop, all right?
我本来要约她出去的  结果这个鲨鱼人
I was gonna ask her out, and then a man-shark
差点把我吃了  威尔斯博士二号又突然出现
tried to eat me, and then Dr. Wells the sequel showed up.
我们能不能不叫他威尔斯博士
Okay, can we not use the name "Dr. Wells"?
我觉得叫他哈里就行
I'm just gonna call him "Harry."
好的  那就哈里
Okay. Harry, yeah.
你总是会遇见别的哈里
Listen, there's always gonna be Harrys out there,
可是你不能让这些来自平行世界的人
but you can't let the Harrys of the world
扰乱了你现在的生活
get in the way of you living your life.
去约帕蒂吧
Ask Patty out.
你得大胆一些
You gotta-- you gotta be bold.
你说的倒是好听
That's tough talk.
你上次问女生电话号码是什么时候
When was the last time you asked a girl for her number?
看我教你
Watch and learn.
我看着呢
I'm watching.
你好  有什么需要的吗
Hi. What can I get you?
-你好  -你好
- Hi, there. - Hi...again.
你想喝咖啡吗
Do you want some coffee?
我要点咖啡
Yeah, I'll get some coffee.
不  我不想喝咖啡
No, uh, no, I don't want coffee.
你知道我想要什么吗
You know what I do want though?
我要问你一件事
I want to ask you this.
你愿意跟我约会吗
Do you want to go out with me?
我们可以一起喝咖啡什么的
To--we--I mean, we could go get coffee or we--
不
No.
看来你是不愿意了
That's a no.
完全没关系  没关系
That's totally cool. It's cool.
我不骚扰你了
Respect.
中城银行
老兄  你还好吗  拒绝你是她的损失
Yo, dude, you good? It's her loss.
你怎么了
Hey, what's up?
又出现了一个缺口
We have another breach.
什么  你怎么知道的
What? How do you know?
就在中城银行  你现在就得过去
Central City Bank. You gotta go now!
好吧
All right.
你动静挺大啊
You got my attention.
闪电侠
Flash.
她的名字叫做光博士
Her name is Doctor Light.
在我的地球  原本只是个小贼
Small-time thief on my Earth
后来她接触到了粒子加速器的暗物质
until exposure to the dark matter from the Particle Accelerator
成为了超能力者  她的能力是
and became a meta-human with the ability
中城公民报
谁是你的超能力搭档
今日聚焦夺人眼球的光博士
从星光里吸取能量
to derive power from starlight.
真酷
Oh, very cool.
星星的温度能达到5300摄氏度
Stars having a temperature of 5,300 degree Celsius
其散发的亮光能让人失明  要我说
and a blinding luminosity, I would say,
这一点也不酷
"Not very cool at all."
以前那个威尔斯博士可能比较邪恶
You know, our Dr. Wells may have been evil,
而你是个不折不扣的混蛋
but you're just a dick.
很明显  就跟其他人一样
Okay, so obviously, Zoom brought her here
她也是被极速从地球一带过来的
from your Earth like the others.
是啊  现在我们明白了情况
Mm-hmm. Now that we know that,
我们可以利用这种局势
we can use that to gain advantage.
什么意思
What do you mean?
抓住光博士  用她把极速引过来
We capture Doctor Light and use her to lure Zoom here.
你果然疯了
You are insane!
我们不会把极速引到任何地方去
Okay, we are not luring Zoom anywhere!
他们互相认识  而且杰伊很讨厌他
Apparently, they know each other, and Jay is not a fan.
看看这是谁啊
Well, well, well.
像其他人一样
Like everyone else,
我以为地球二的闪电侠已经死了
I assumed Earth-2 Flash was dead.
在这看到杰伊·加里克我怎么一点都不惊讶呢
Why am I not surprised to find Jay Garrick here,
依然活着而且躲极速远远的
still alive and in hiding a full universe away from Zoom?
我没有躲藏
I'm not in hiding.
极速差点杀了我  并准备偷取我的速度
Zoom nearly killed me and stole my speed
然后奇点把我吸到了这里
before the Singularity pulled me here.
-是这样吗  -是这样的
- Is that right? - Yeah, that's right.
不管怎么说  因为你
Well, whatever the case, in your absence,
极速变得能力更强  速度更快
Zoom has only gotten more powerful, faster.
巴里  趁现在还能打过他  你得赶紧动手
Barry, you have to defeat Zoom now while you still can.
不  现在不能这么鲁莽
No, this isn't the time to be reckless.
我们不知道极速为什么把光博士送来
We don't even know why Zoom sent Doctor Light here.
她是个小偷  不是杀手
She's a thief, not a killer.
极速可以使人做出违背本性的事
Zoom can make people do things out of character.
不管是不是小偷  她都会杀了你
Thief or not, she'll kill you.
别吵了  听我说
All right, look, hey,
我们稍后再决定这么对付光博士
we can decide what to do with Light later.
首先  我们要找到她  好吗
First, we have to find her, okay?
你是怎么知道
Hey, how did you know
她闯入银行了
that she was breaking into the bank?
我手机上有示警
I got an alert on my phone.
每次银行有劫案的时候
There is a little ring-a-ding
它就会铃铃地响
every time, like, there's a robbery at a bank.
-什么  -不过你知道吗
- What? - But you know what?
我觉得可以让尖端科研实验室的卫星
I think I can get the S.T.A.R. Labs satellite
扫瞄那些不规则的太阳辐射
to scan for any irregular solar radiation emissions
这样就能找到光博士的光了
and we can find Doctor Light's light.
好  我打电话给乔  看中城警局是否有线索
Okay, I'm gonna also call Joe, see if CCPD has any leads.
我回来之前尽量别让他俩接触
Why don't we keep them apart until I get back?
我想那不会有什么问题的
I am sure that won't be a problem.
中城警局
你的科学研究怎么样了
How's your science stuff?
完成了
I finished it.
你的报告写完了吗
Um, did you get your report done?
是的  写完了
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
自己写报告的确挺无趣的  不过...
It wasn't as much fun writing it by myself, but...
-回头见  -好
- I'll see ya. - Yeah.
你是否有过这样压抑的感觉
Hey, do you ever feel completely overwhelmed
很多事情都要在一天内完成
by everything that you have to do in a day
但唯一一件
and it feels like the one thing
你真正想做的事却没有做
that you actually want to do is the thing that gets lost?
我没听懂你的话
I'm confused. What?
我想了很久  不过现在终于能说出来了
I've been thinking, for a while now actually,
你是否愿意找时间跟我一起吃个饭
would you want to get dinner with me sometime?
这不会又是像以前那样
Yeah, this isn't gonna be one those things
我兴高采烈的去了  结果
where I get really excited and then, you know,
你又跟我说一大堆高科技的东西吧
more science stuff comes up, right?
不  不会的  明天怎么样
No, no, that's not-- um, tomorrow?
我们早一点吃晚饭
We can grab an early dinner.
我不想再等了
I don't want to wait anymore.
-好  -好  我很期待
- Okay.  - Okay. Looking forward to it.
尖端科研实验室
灾难一个月后
哈里
Hey, Harry.
在这
Hey, over here.
请进  随便用我的工作室和电脑
Come inside. Use my workroom. Use my computer!
-我不介意  -谢谢
- I don't care! - Thanks.
你和威尔斯本体的音乐品味真不一样
You and Wells prime have very different musical tastes.
他的更好一点
His were better.
这个哈里森·威尔斯跟我不一样
This Harrison Wells and I are very different
但在某些方面很相似
but similar in some respects.
他在粒子加速器上的失误
I see he made almost the same mistake I did
跟我犯的一样
with the Particle Accelerator.
他做了很多坏事
He did a lot of terrible things,
没有一件是出于失误而造成的
and none of them were by mistake.
他对你做了什么
What did he do to you?
我知道他制造了奇点
I know he caused the Singularity,
杀了巴里的母亲  还有一大堆什么的
murdered Barry's mother, blah, blah, blah, blah.
他对你做了什么
What did he do to you?
你都不敢直视我的眼睛
You can barely look me in the eye.
为什么  他对你做了什么
Why is that? What did he do to you?
他把手伸进了我的身体里
He shoved his hand through my chest.
他停止了我的心跳
He stopped my heart.
真疼  好吧  难怪会这样
Ouch, okay, that would do it,
但你也活过来了啊
but you survived that.
因为巴里清除了那条时间线
Only because Barry erased that timeline.
知道了  巴里做过时间旅行
I see. Barry traveled in time.
两次
Twice.
-这样吧  -你想怎么样
- Here's how it is. - What's the deal?
你不必非要喜欢我
You don't have to like me.
我不喜欢你
I don't like you,
但你必须跟我联手阻止极速和光博士
but you have to work with me to stop Zoom and Doctor Light.
你能做到吗
Can you do that?
走着瞧呗
I guess we'll see, won't we?
好吧
I guess we will.
还有一件事
One more thing--
你说你要重设尖端科研实验室的卫星
you said you were going to re-task the S.T.A.R. Labs satellite?
为了扫瞄太阳辐射  是的  已经完成了
To scan for solar emissions, yeah, we're up and running.
我想检查一下你的程序
I'd like to examine your program.
我要看看是否管用
I want to see if it works.
别担心  会管用的
Don't worry. It'll work.
哈里开始惹我讨厌了
Harry's starting to get on my nerves.
中城银行的无声警报刚才启动了
The silent alarm just went off at the Bank of Central City.
-那一定是光博士  -可能是个陷阱
- That's gotta be Doctor Light. - Could be a trap.
巴里  相信我  光博士不是杀手
Barry, trust me, Doctor Light is not a killer.
-你可以跟她谈谈  -好
- You can talk to her. - Okay.
在找这个吗
Looking for this?
我知道极速派你来杀我
I know Zoom sent you here to kill me.
好消息是  你不必那样做了
Good news, you don't have to do that.
除非我可以带着那笔现金出城
Not if I can get out of town with that cash.
然后怎样
And then what?
极速可不会喜欢看到你背弃他的  是不是
Zoom's not gonna like that you ditched him, right?
我和我朋友可以帮你
My friends and I can help you.
没人可以保护我免受极速威胁
Nobody can protect me from Zoom!
好了  我们把光放低点如何
All right, why don't we take it down a little minute,
来一次正常的谈话
have a normal conversation,
好吗
all right?
感谢
Thank you.
琳达
Linda?
-琳达·帕克  -你怎么知道我的名字
- Linda Park? - How do you know my name?
我不明白
I don't understand.
这是个错误
This was a mistake.
巴里  出什么事了
Barry, what's happening?
我看不见了
I can't see.
伙计们  我看不见了
Guys, I can't see.
我还是看不见呀
I still can't see.
这要持续多久
How long is this gonna last?
你遭受的是日光性视网膜病变
You're suffering from solar retinopathy.
你的视网膜已经严重损坏
Your retinas are severely damaged.
你该庆幸不是永久性失明
You're lucky you're not permanently blind.
但由于你有快速再生能力
But with your rapid regeneration abilities,
你的视力应该很快会恢复
your sight should return soon.
据我估算要6.25小时
6.25 hours by my estimation.
如果你直接阻止光博士  而不是和她聊天
All this could have been avoided if you just stopped Light
这一切都不会发生
instead of chitchatting with her.
她是趁巴里没有防备
She caught Barry off guard.
你总能找到借口
Always an excuse with you, right?
他是世上最快的人  她怎么可能伤到他
He's the fastest man alive. How could she possibly do that?
因为光博士长得很像我前女友
Because Light looks exactly like my ex-girlfriend,
琳达·帕克
Linda Park.
所以极速派她来了  他知道你会迟疑
That's why Zoom sent her-- because he knew you'd hesitate.
这说明极速肯定知道你的前女友是琳达
That means Zoom had to have known somehow that Linda was your ex.
所以巴里现在必须采取行动
Which is why Barry has to act now,
趁极速派来另一个他熟悉的人之前
before Zoom sends another double from Barry's life.
好的  可现在我更担心的是琳达
All right, right now, I'm more worried about Linda.
当我看到面具下的脸时  我叫了她的名字
When I saw who was under the mask, I said her name.
万一光博士在我不小心说出名字前
What if Light didn't even realize that
还不知道她在这世界有个二重身呢
she had a doppelganger here until I accidentally told her?
原子粉碎者穿过缺口时
The first thing that Atom Smasher did
第一件事就是杀掉他的二重身
when he crossed the breach was to kill his doppelganger.
没错  但光博士不是原子粉碎者
Yeah, but Light's not like Atom Smasher.
我们应该留意下本地琳达
We should keep an eye on your Linda.
好的  我去
All right, I'll go.
抱歉
Sorry.
-哥们  -巴里
- Bro. - Barry!
-怎么了  -巴里  好了
- What? Ooh! - Barry, Barry, Okay, okay.
在视力恢复前你什么都不能做
You can't do anything until your sight returns.
不行  不行  来扶着这个小栏杆
No, no, no, come on, here's the little rail here.
-让我去吧  -我和你一起
- I'll do it. - I'll go with you!
-巴里  -你好
- Hey, Barry! - Hey.
我一听说就尽快...
I came as soon as I heard--
你和他一模一样
You look just like him.
我猜我的替身也做了冒犯她的事对吧
I'm guessing my counterpart did something to offend her as well?
她的未婚夫因他而死
Her fianc died because of him.
爱瑞丝  我知道看见他感觉很怪
Iris, I know it's weird seeing him.
最近确实有很多事要消化
Yeah, it's just a lot to process lately.
威尔斯  我妈妈
Wells, my mother.
对了  你现在好些了吗
How are you doing with that, by the way?
现在她已经走了
I mean, now that she's gone,
还好
okay.
好吧  爱瑞斯  听着
Yeah, Iris, um, look--
谢谢
Thanks.
你知道你可以和我谈谈的
You know you can talk to me about it.
我知道的  但我真的没事了
Yeah, I know, but really, I'm fine, okay?
我该问问你怎么样了
I should be asking how you're doing.
是找我的  我去拿
That's me. I got it.
-巴里  我帮你  -我能行
- Barry, let me help you. - I got it.
好吧
All right.
"得晚一点了  -P"
Uh, "Running a little late. P."
P是谁
Who's P?
P...
P.
-是帕蒂  -我爸爸的搭档帕蒂
- That's Patty. - My dad's partner Patty?
她要晚点去哪里
What is she running late for?
我们的第一次约会
Um, our first date.
这很好啊  她很好
That's so great! She's great.
帕蒂是很好  只是你懂的
Yeah, no, Patty's great. I just, you know--
我很怀疑在我取消这次约会后
I doubt she's gonna give me another shot
她还会不会再给我一次机会了
when I have to cancel on her.
别取消
Don't cancel.
我看不见  爱瑞斯  真正的蒙眼约会
I'm blind, Iris. A literal blind date.
肯定行不通的
It's not gonna work.
我们可是在尖端科研实验室啊
Hey, we are in S.T.A.R. Labs.
拜托  这里肯定有
Come on, there's gotta be something here
能帮你顺利度过今晚的东西
that can help you through the night.
是的
Yeah.
或...人
Or someone.
西斯科
Cisco, hey!
-在你左边  另一边  -西斯科
- To your left. Other left. - Cisco.
抱歉
Sorry.
sorry.
好了  她就在你面前两步的地方
Okay. She's two steps in front of you.
墨镜不错啊
Nice glasses.
-触地得分  -抱歉我来晚了
- Touchdown. - I'm so sorry I'm late.
不  别在意
No, don't be.
实际上我评判约会对像
You know, I actually judge my dates
是看对方有没有放我鸽子
on whether or not they stand me up,
所以你的开端表现很好
so you are off to a great start.
什么意思  哪有人会放你鸽子
What do you mean? Who would stand you up?
我可是名声在外
Oh, I have a reputation.
不是那种名声  我不是那个意思
Not that kind of reputation. That's not what I meant.
好囧
That's embarrassing.
其实  我曾经逮捕过一个男朋友
You know, I actually-- I arrested a boyfriend once.
很久以前的男朋友  在我吃饭的时候
A very ex-boyfriend, while we were at dinner.
他喝高了  开始侮辱女服务生
He got really wasted and decided to insult the waitress,
所以我以公共场合酗酒罪逮捕了他
so I cited him for public intoxication.
-太搞笑了  -是的
- That is hilarious. - Yeah.
很奇特
Special.
那么...
So...
哥们  她太漂亮了
Dude, she looks amazing.
你要告诉她她看起来美极了
You have to tell her how amazing she looks.
你很漂亮  帕蒂
You look amazing, Patty.
谢谢  其实我纠结了很久
Uh, thanks, I actually had a really hard time
不知道要穿些什么
trying to figure out what to wear,
我不知道是不是该穿裙子
like, if I should wear a dress
还是这颜色有点怪
or if this color was a little weird.
没  你很漂亮
No, you look great.
嗯  不  这是什么颜色呢
Um, yeah, no, that-- what would you call that color?
看不出来
I can't tell.
-镜头是黑白的  -我不知道
- The feed's black and white. - I don't know.
不管叫什么颜色
Yeah, whatever it is,
这颜色都该感谢你把它穿在身上
that color should thank you for wearing it.
兜得妙
My man.
-真会说  -还行吧
- Smooth. - Not smooth.
红酒单来了  开始点单
Oh, wine list. Here we go.
好的  谢谢
yes, uh, got it. Thank you.
不如你...
Um, you know, why don't you-
-抱歉  -没事
- Sorry. - No, that's okay.
男生老是挑三拣四的  不如你选吧
The guy always picks. Why don't you choose?
行啊  想喝什么  红酒还是白酒
Yeah, what do you want, red or white?
你喜欢的都行
Whatever you'd like.
你都搞定了  还要我做什么
You got this. Why do you even need me?
-给  -谢谢
- Here you go. - Thank you.
经典的监视饮品
Classic stakeout fuel.
没错
Yeah.
你的地球上有咖啡吧
You have coffee on your Earth, right?
我想咖啡是多重宇宙中唯一不变的事物
I think coffee's the one constant in the multiverse.
我不是想打探
So I don't mean to pry,
但是威尔斯不断提到你和极速的时候
but when Wells keeps referring to you and Zoom,
他到底在说什么
what's he talking about?
我和极速交手过很多次
I fought Zoom many times,
每次我都是勉强逃命
each time barely escaping with my life.
所以  是啊
So yeah.
也许我是没有每次都挺身而出
Maybe I didn't always confront him when I should have.
事实上  极速吓到我了
Truth is, Zoom scared me.
他从我这偷走了我最宝贵的神速力
He stole the most precious thing from me: my speed.
我不想巴里也遭受这样的命运
I didn't want Barry to suffer the same fate.
也许如果你和威尔斯坐下来
Well, maybe if you just sat down with Wells,
好好谈谈
talked to him about it...
不  千万不要相信威尔斯  凯特琳
No, no, no. Do not trust Wells, Caitlin.
这人非常乐意利用他的科技应用
The guy was more than happy to make money
来从超能力者这件事上赚钱
off the meta-human problem with his tech apps,
而如今他对极速着迷
and now he's obsessed with Zoom.
有些事情变了
Something has changed
而且不只是因为我销声匿迹了
and not just because I disappeared.
我不相信威尔斯  我相信你
Well, I don't trust Wells. I trust you.
其实我一直非常想问你
So I've actually been dying to ask you,
被闪电击中是什么感觉
what was it like to be struck by lightning?
改变人生  说实话
Life-changing, to be honest.
疼吗
Did it hurt?
我真的只记得感觉到电流
I mean, all I really remember is feeling electricity
从头到脚冲击着我的身体
surging through my body.
那是一种我从未感受过的强度
It was an intensity I had never felt,
我好像立刻与周围的一切产生了连接
like I was instantly connected to everything around me.
然后九个月后  我从昏迷中醒来
Then I woke up from a coma nine months later.
就那样在未来醒过来
Waking up in the future like that,
好像是时空穿梭一样
it's like time travel.
-有点像  -嗯
- Sort of, yeah. - Yeah.
在我九岁的时候  我溺过水
When I was nine, I actually drowned.
我的头撞到跳板
I hit my head on the diving board
然后我掉进泳池里
and fell into the swimming pool.
心脏停止跳动有...
Uh, my heart stopped for, I think,
两分钟吧  直到我爸爸把我救上来
two minutes until my dad rescued me and saved my life.
是啊
Yeah.
看来我们俩都摆了死亡一道
So I guess we've both cheated death.
我在人生中经历过的一些事
I've been through a few things in my life
教会了我不要害怕任何事物
that taught me not to be afraid of anything.
我想人们就是因为害怕
I think fear is what holds people back
才不敢去做真实的自己
from being who they should be.
说教啊
Ugh, preach!
没错  我还在这里  诡异地在偷窥
Yeah, I'm still here, creepin' and peepin'.
没事吧
You okay?
抱歉  我只是...非常同意你的话
Sorry, I just-- yeah, I really agree with that.
真的吗
Really?
我还在想另一件事  我认为你看不到我
I think another thing, too, I think you can't see me.
-中止  -什么  你说什么
- Abort! - What? What do you mean?
我认为你看不到我
I think you can't see me.
拜托  如果我连这都没发现
Come on, I would not be a good detective
那我就不是个优秀的警探
if I couldn't have figured this one out.
我不知道
I don't know.
-是的  -嗯
- Uh, yeah. - Yeah.
真是遗憾  也很尴尬
I'm really sorry and embarrassed
没和你说这件事
I didn't say anything.
-之前我的瞳孔扩张  -巴里
- I had my pupils dilated earlier. - Barry.
-我的老天  -巴里
- Oh, my God! - Barry!
我真的不想取消这次约会
And I really didn't want to cancel.
巴里  我看不到了
Barry! I lost my eyes!
不  你笑得很甜
No, you have a great smile.
真的吗  你怎么知道我在笑
Really, how do you know I'm smiling?
只是直觉
Just a hunch.
你我的世界还有什么别的不同
Okay, so what else is different about our worlds?
你们那有大溪地吗
Do you have Tahiti?
从未去过  但我很喜欢亚特兰蒂斯
Never been, but I do love Atlantis.
就是那个沉入了海洋深处的岛屿
As in the lost city submerged in the ocean somewhere?
在我的地球上它其实是露出海面的
Well, it's actually above water on my Earth.
我有个朋友就是那的人
One of my best friends is from there.
真想去看看
I would love to see it.
那里很美
It's special.
那种地方去了就不想再离开
It's the kind of place you never want to leave.
你好啊  美女
Hello, gorgeous.
-所有人出去  马上  -快走
- Everybody out, now! - Go!
快走  快走  快点
Go, go, go. Go, move, quick.
-你留下  -不行
- Except you. - I don't think so.
不行  她得跟我们一起走
No, no, she's leaving with us.
-今天不行  -你想从我这得到什么
- Not today. - What do you want from me?
你的命
Your life.
是光博士
Doctor Light.
不好  快去
Oh, no. Go.
我从未杀过人
I've never killed anyone before,
可要是你的二重身杀了你就不算是谋杀了  对吧
but it's not murder if it's your double, right?
你为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this?
这是我能活下来的唯一方式
It's the only way that I can stay alive.
就是变成你
To become you.
抱歉了  琳达
I'm sorry, Linda.
不要
No!
-这怎么可能  -你不会理解的
- How is this possible? - You couldn't understand.
光博士
Light!
闪电侠
Flash.
我还以为刚才把我干掉了呢
I thought I took care of you outside.
千万别松手  我会摔倒的
Please don't let go. I may trip.
好吧  我保证不会
Okay, I won't. I promise.
还有两个台阶
Two more steps.
-少走了一个  -可以了
- All right. Missed one. - There you go.
真好玩  我们直接跳到了牵手这一步
It's funny how we skipped straight to the hand-holding part.
是啊
Yes.
我们已经走到我车这了
We have arrived at my car, so--
那你觉得我们到亲晚安吻的阶段了吗
Well, do you think we've reached the good night kiss stage?
顺便说下  这是衣服是酒红色
This is burgundy, by the way,
穿你身上很漂亮
and you look great in it.
-这会你能看见了  -是的
- Now you can see? - I can.
一定是这个吻起作用了
That must have been some kiss.
我想是的
I guess so.
-抱歉  -没事  我的也响了
- Sorry. - No, it's mine too.
好奇怪  喂  西斯科
Weird. Cisco, hey.
长官
Sir?
我看到了我自己
I saw myself.
这怎么可能
How is that even possible?
看来你有个邪恶的超能力双胞胎
Sounds like you have an evil meta-twin.
拉金是因为
And now Larkin's dead
有个长得跟我很像的人想要杀我才送命的
because someone who looks like me wanted to kill me?
琳达  这件事不怪你
Linda, none of this is your fault.
我保证我们会查明真相的
We're gonna figure it all out, I promise.
你还好吧
How you doing?
多亏了爱瑞丝  我才活着
I'm alive, thanks to Iris.
看来她文武双全
Turns out she's as badass with a gun as she is with a pen.
她确实是
Yeah, she is.
你安全了就好
I'm just happy that you're safe.
安全起见  我给你安排了
I've arranged a security detail
全天候的安保人员
around the clock, just to be sure.
你准备好了我就带你过去
I can take you to them if you're ready.
好的
Yeah.
都怪我  我本该在这的
This is because of me. I should've been here.
巴里  你之前看不见的
Barry, you were blind.
什么忙你也帮不上
There's nothing that you could have done.
你觉得这个面具能帮我们找到那女的吗
You think this mask can help us find that woman?
这上面的任何证据都会和琳达的吻合
Any evidence on this is just gonna match Linda.
我再想别的办法
I'll think of something else.
不会让光博士再杀人了
Light's not gonna kill again.
凯特琳  你们还好吧
Caitlin, are you guys okay?
-还好  -对不起  巴里
- Yeah. - Barry, I'm sorry.
光博士从未杀过人
Doctor Light's never killed before.
我以为我可以跟她讲道理
I thought we could reason with her.
不要和一个受极速影响的人讲道理
You cannot reason with someone under Zoom's influence,
现如今有人因你而死  加里克
and now a man is dead because of you, Garrick.
这一切都因你而起
This whole thing is because of you.
他因为你而怀疑自己
He doubts himself because of you,
相信我  巴里可以做到你做不到的事
but believe me, Barry can do what you could not.
巴里可以阻止极速
Barry can stop Zoom.
我花了两年时间追捕极速
I spent two years hunting Zoom.
错  是极速追捕你
Wrong! Zoom hunted you!
你用生命中过去的两年时间
You spent the last two years of your life
逃跑  逃跑  逃离极速
running, running, running from Zoom.
如果你让巴里走上这条路
Zoom would have killed me just like he will kill Barry
极速会像差点杀了我那样杀掉巴里
if you lead him down this path!
不会的  因为他跟你不一样
No, because he is not like you.
巴里直面危险  而不是躲避
Barry runs towards danger, not from it,
因为他不是懦夫
because Barry's not a coward.
够了
Enough!
你刚才对杰伊太苛刻了
You were pretty hard on Jay in there.
也许你也该对他苛刻点
Maybe you should be hard on Jay too.
我见识过你的能耐了  巴里
I've seen what you can do, Barry.
我计算过你跑得有多快
I've calculated how fast you can run,
应该是你指导杰伊  而不是他指导你
and you should be teaching Jay, not the other way around.
在我得知另一个威尔斯
You know, before I learned that the other Wells
是杀害我母亲的凶手前  我很尊敬他
was the man who murdered my mom, I looked up to him.
其实他曾是我的导师
He was my mentor, actually.
也就是说  我的二重身
So my doppelganger,
那个长得跟我一模一样的人
a man who looks exactly like me,
他背叛了你
betrayed you.
对不起  我不是他
I'm sorry, I'm not him,
所以你得相信我
so you need to listen to me
我觉得你能搞定极速
when I say you can take care of Zoom,
而我们只要抓住光博士就行了
and all we have to do is capture Doctor Light.
我想过在面具上检测光博士的DNA
I thought about testing the mask for Light's DNA,
但只会出现琳达的
but it would only have Linda's.
面具  什么面具
The mask, what mask?
光博士的面具
Light's mask.
你怎么拿到这个的
How did you get this?
爱瑞斯在光博士袭击琳达的时候射下来的
Iris shot it off Doctor Light when she attacked Linda.
你知道怎么用这个面具来找光博士
You know how to use the mask to find Light?
是  我知道
Yes, I do.
我们只要把这个给他就行了
All we have to do is give it to him.
为什么给我
Why me?
因为你有超能力
Because you have powers.
你在说什么啊
What are you talking about?
我发明了这个手表以发现超能力者
I developed this watch to detect meta-humans.
你从未在手机上收到警报提示
You never got an alert on your phone.
没有给尖端科技研究实验室的卫星重新编程
You never reprogrammed the S.T.A.R. Labs satellite,
这就是原因所在
and this is why.
他是个超能力者
He's a meta-human.
西斯科  你知道这事
Cisco, have you known about this,
但你没告诉我们吗
and you didn't say anything to us?
我本来是想告诉你们的
Yeah, I was gonna tell you.
多谢你了  哈里
Thanks a lot, Harry.
我发誓我想说的  但没说出口
I swear I was, but I didn't.
我只是  我害怕了
I was just-- I was afraid.
害怕什么
Afraid of what?
威尔斯博士说暗物质赐予了我这份天赋
Dr. Wells said the dark matter gave me this, this gift.
他说有朝一日我会因此感谢他的
He said that one day I'd thank him for it.
如果我变成他那样该怎么办
What if I become like him?
西斯科  我觉得我们任何一个人
Cisco, I don't think any of us would become evil,
都不会因为突然得到超能力而变得邪恶
if we all of sudden got powers,
哪怕是从威尔斯博士那里得到的
even if they were from Dr. Wells.
是啊  也许你是对的
Yeah, maybe you're right.
我应该跟你们说的
I should have said something.
这是我的错  对不起
That's my fault. I'm sorry.
你可以等会再抱歉
Well, you can be sorry later,
因为现在
because right now,
我们要用你的超能力来找光博士
we have to use your powers to find Doctor Light.
西斯科  你的超能力  怎么用
Cisco, your abilities, how do they work?
我有时候会有些感觉
I get these feelings sometimes,
这些震波  我能看到那些缺口
these vibes, visions of the breachers
出现在地球上时的影像
when they come to this Earth.
我只是  我不知道是什么触发了超能力
I just-- I'm not sure what triggers it.
有时候它就那么发生了
Sometimes it just happens.
有时是在我碰到他们的东西的时候
Sometimes it's when I'm touching something of theirs.
碰下这个面具
Touch the mask.
你要想找到光博士就赶紧碰它
You want to find Doctor Light, do it.
我觉得好像没起效
I don't think it's working.
再试一次
Try again.
Try again!
-对不起  没有反应  -再试
- I'm sorry, it's not. - Again!
-我控制不了它  -那是因为你害怕
- I can't control it. - Because you're afraid.
我说了我不知道怎么触发超能力
I'm telling you I don't know how it works!
不是我想用就能用的
I can't just make it happen!
我告诉你  你可以的
I'm telling you, yes, you can!
火车站南广场  十五号站台
South Plaza Train Station, Platform 15.
你们还在等什么
What are you waiting for?
各位  站台这里人太多了
Guys, the platform's crowded.
你们确定她在这吗
Are you sure she's here?
她应该穿着一件黑风衣
She should be wearing a black trench coat.
黑色风衣  找到她了
Black trench coat. Found her.
所有人  离开这里  快  快走
Everybody, get out of here. Go, go, hurry!
你为什么就不能放我走呢
Why won't you just let me leave?
我不能放你走  你杀了一个无辜的人
I can't let you leave. You killed an innocent man.
那是个意外
That was an accident.
蓄意谋杀琳达·帕克可不是
Trying to kill Linda Park wasn't.
这是我摆脱极速的唯一方式
It's the only way that I can be free from Zoom,
除非我杀了你
unless I kill you.
我也不能让你这么做
I can't let you do that either,
所以我们俩有问题要解决了
so we've got a problem.
走着瞧吧
We'll see.
各位  应该在我来之前就讨论这个的
Guys, should have talked about this before I left,
我该怎么阻止她呢
but how should I stop her?
不断尝试不同的角度  巴里
Keep trying different angles, Barry.
找到她的盲点
Find her blind spot.
我没法足够接近她  我该怎么办
I can't get close enough. What should I do?
我不知道
I don't know.
坦白地说
I gotta tell ya,
这可不是我想听到的答案
that's not exactly the answer I was looking for.
你需要声东击西
You need to confuse her.
给她不止一个目标
Give her more than one target,
这样她就不知道该攻击谁了
so she does not know who to fire at.
好的  我怎么才能做到呢
All right, how do I do that?
你跑得足够快
By running so fast,
就能创造出你的多重余象
you create multiple afterimages of yourself,
制造出一个速度幻象
you create a speed mirage.
你说什么幻象  我从来没跑过那么快
A wha-- speed mir-- I've never run that fast.
我可是听说
Well, from what I've been told,
你曾经进行过时间旅行
you've traveled through time.
你的速度肯定够快
You'll be more than fast enough.
好吧
Okay.
-巴里  -我做不到
- Barry? - I can't do it.
你可以的  巴里  威尔斯博士是对的
Yes, you can, Barry. Hey, Dr. Wells is right.
你很快  比从前的我快得多
You are fast, faster than I ever was
也会比以后的我强得多
and better than I ever will be.
别重蹈我的覆辙  被恐惧和疑虑所束缚
Don't let fear and doubt hold you back like it did to me.
你是闪电侠  巴里
You're The Flash, Barry.
让光博士看看你的厉害
Show Light what that means.
你在哪
Where are you?
我就在这
I'm right here.
光博士已经被安全关进管道监狱了
Doctor Light is safely locked in the Pipeline.
干得好
Nicely done.
威尔斯  谢谢你帮巴里把光博士抓起来了
Wells, thank you for helping Barry put away Doctor Light.
那现在要怎么做
So what now?
我们照威尔斯博士说的做
We do what Dr. Wells said.
我们用她引来极速  然后彻底做个了结
We use her to lure Zoom here, end this once and for all.
你开玩笑的吧
You can't be serious.
更多的缺口会出现
More breachers are gonna come.
更多无辜的人会送命
More innocent people may die.
我不能让这种事再发生了
I can't let this happen anymore.
你这么做是错的
You're making a mistake.
极速是个无法醒来的噩梦
Okay, Zoom is a nightmare you can't wake up from.
我已经面对过我最可怕的噩梦了
I've already had my worst nightmare.
他的名字是逆闪电
His name was Reverse-Flash,
我有很长时间都在惧怕他
and I spent a long time being afraid of him.
但我已经不再害怕了
I'm not gonna be afraid anymore.
好吧  巴里
Okay, Barry.
你也许比我快
You may be faster than me,
但是你还没有准备好去单独对抗极速
but you're not ready to fight Zoom by yourself.
没错  杰伊
That's just it, Jay.
我不会独自去对抗他
I'm not gonna fight him by myself.
我有大家的帮助
I've got all of them to help me.
我有威尔斯博士
I've got Dr. Wells.
我还有你
I've got you.
不  我不能违背良心帮助你
No, I can't in good conscience help you when I know
因为我知道最后的结果只能是你失去速度
it'll only lead to you losing your speed,
甚至更糟
or even worse,
死亡
your death.
看来乐观主义只在地球一上存在
Optimism must be an Earth-1 thing.
你们都要问问自己  为什么多年来这个人
You all need to ask yourself why this man, for years,
都没有承认他需要
wouldn't admit that he was responsible
为粒子加速器爆炸负责
for the Particle Accelerator exploding underground.
他也许不是你们地球上的哈里森·威尔斯
He may not be Harrison Wells from your Earth,
但他就和你认识的那个一样有很多秘密
but he has just as many secrets as the one you knew.
杰伊  请别走
Jay, please don't go.
我很抱歉  凯特琳
I'm so sorry, Caitlin.
祝你一天愉快
Have a nice day.
请问你有什么需要
What can I get you?
超级尴尬  我知道
Yeah, I know, this is supes awkward,
也许我比你感觉还要尴尬
probably more for me than for you,
我只想点杯咖啡  好吗
but I just want coffee, okay?
三杯闪电侠  其中一杯要低咖啡因
Just three Flashes, one of them decaf.
就这样
That's it.
你确定你就想要这些吗
Are you sure that's all you want?
太有意思了
Oh, that's funny.
你还想再冲我开一枪吗
You just want to shoot me down again?
不  不  不
No, no, no, no.
我的意思是  我刚搬到中城
What I mean is, I just moved to Central City,
对我来说是个很大的改变
and it's a pretty big change from where I come from.
这里的一切都那么新那么壮观
Everything here is so big and new
而且到处都是超能力者
and filled with meta-humans.
好吧  但是考虑上这个城市的规模
Yeah, well, when you factor in the size of the city,
你想要撞上一个超能力者的机会
the chances of running into a meta-human are
实际上还挺小的
actually pretty low.
我的意思是
I guess what I'm trying to say is,
那天你让我有点措手不及
you kinda caught me off guard the other day,
但是现在我已经做好准备了
but now I'm a little more prepared,
所以我想确定下  你只想要咖啡吗
so I just want to make sure, is coffee all you want?
你好  我是西斯科·拉蒙
Hi, I'm Cisco Ramon.
肯德拉·桑德斯
Kendra Saunders.
很高兴认识你
It's nice to meet you.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
没事  我只是
Yeah, I just--
我只是已经习惯了杰伊是团队的一员
I was getting used to Jay being part of the team.
好吧  杰伊是个英雄
Well, look, Jay is a hero.
英雄总会在你需要的时候出现
They always seem to show up just when you need 'em.
看看这个
Peep that.
小伙子  看到我是怎么做的了吧
That's how it's done, young Padawan.
-不错啊  -下周就去约会
- Nice. - Going on a date next week.
西斯科·拉蒙重回战场了
Things are looking up for Cisco Ramon.
我想是吧
I guess so.
虽然还有这些超能力的问题
Still stuck with these powers, though.
我不知道该拿它们怎么办
Just don't know how to feel about 'em.
听着
Hey, look,
你不是一个人
you don't gotta go through it alone.
现在你所需要的是一个炫酷的名字
And now you need a cool name.
没错  你说的太对了
Oh, snap! You're totally right.
我得好好想想
I gotta think about this one.
你们了解我的  这得是个完美的名字
Well, you know me. It's gotta be perfect.
一个非常上口的名字
Something that really sings, you know?
比如像是
Something like--
震波
Vibe?
Vibe.
震波
地球二
你父亲已经抛弃你了
Your father has abandoned you.
你在撒谎
You're lying!
我父亲是世上最聪明的人
My father's the smartest man alive.
他会找到我  拯救我  然后杀了你
He'll find me, he'll save me, and then he'll kill you.
我不会死
I will not die.
但你和你父亲的下场
What happens to you and your father
现在还不确定
is still to be decided.